https://www.boroguide.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Clubs2020-1 OpponentsClubs ArchiveClub RecordsPlayers2020-1 Boro’ SquadPlayers ArchivePlayer RecordsSeasons2020-1 SeasonSeasons ArchiveSeason RecordsLongest RunsFeaturesSt Woking DayWhy We BotherBetting On StevenageLinksA Load Of Old ToffeeAbout UsAbout UsAdvertise With UsCookies PolicyMissing Match DataPress and MediaPrivacy Policy
Search
Friday 11 December 2020AboutAdvertiseCookiesPressPrivacy
BoroGuide
Clubs2020-1 OpponentsClubs ArchiveClub RecordsPlayers2020-1 Boro’ SquadPlayers ArchivePlayer RecordsSeasons2020-1 SeasonSeasons ArchiveSeason RecordsLongest RunsFeaturesSt Woking DayWhy We BotherBetting On StevenageLinksA Load Of Old ToffeeAbout UsAbout UsAdvertise With UsCookies PolicyMissing Match DataPress and MediaPrivacy Policy
Home » Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyOur Privacy PolicyThis is the privacy policy for BoroGuide [www.boroguide.co.uk]… or the “website”, just to keep things nice and simple later on. It ain’t the most riveting read you’ll stumble across on here, but it does set out what we do to protect your privacy.It goes without saying that our privacy policy applies to all parts of this website (see, told you it keeps things nice and simple).Here at BoroGuide, we’re dead keen on respecting and protecting your personal info. We don’t actually ask for or collect your details that often. There are, however, a few things that we need to make you aware of for your own benefit. And to comply with the law, y’know… Why Do We Collect Info From You?Don’t panic. We don’t want to stalk you. Any information we collect from you is mainly to make this website better. Some information we collect will help us monitor performance of pages and features; other information is used to display adverts that might be of interest to you. What Info Do We Collect From You?There are a few ways we collect information from you, which are:Cookies that provide us with details about your visit to BoroGuide. We can’t use any of this info to identify you as a person, however. We’re talking about location, your device (desktop or mobile) and other similar stats; stuff that informs our website experience. For more about this, see our Cookies Policy.If you’re interested in advertising on BoroGuide, we provide a form for you to get in touch. This asks for a name, email address and message. We need this information so we can get back to you and talk to you about our advertising options etc.Our email address can be found in places if you need to get in touch with us. That applies to advertising or media enquiries, as well as general contact. Again, we need at least an email address from you if you were hoping for us to respond to you.Our blog provides you with the facility to comment. You don’t have to provide your name or email address; we give you the option to provide it if you want to display your details with your comment. We guess it depends how profound you think your musings are? Your ConsentWe don’t use your personal information for direct marketing activities, but we will use it to contact you if you’ve filled out a form or emailed us in the first instance. If you do reach out to us, you’re welcome to request that we delete your personal information at any point. And if you comment on our blog, you’re free to delete it. This also removes your personal data.In accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation, you *must* consent to providing your personal information when filling out a form on our website or commenting on one of our articles. We will also give you the ability to opt-out from receiving the cookies we use on this site. For any questions, email us and we’ll do our best to help: editor@boroguide.co.uk How We Protect Your PrivacyIt may be the case that we transfer your information to locations outside the EU for processing and storing. To give you an example, data that we collect via Google Analytics may well be transferred to the US and held on Google servers. By providing your info, you agree to this transfer. That said, we will take all reasonable steps to make sure your data is kept secure and in compliance with our privacy policy.The data that you provide us with is stored on secure servers. We can’t completely guarantee the safety of this information, but we’re confident that we’re quite low risk when it comes to hacking efforts.Our website also has a number of links to other websites, which we do not control. We cannot and will not take any responsibility for how you use those websites, and how any information you supply to those websites is then used. Our privacy policy extends to the outer reaches of BoroGuide and BoroGuide alone. And, no, we’re not responsible for Borochat. That ship has long since sailed… Website RecordingWe use Google Analytics to help us track what you are looking at when you visit BoroGuide. No personal data is collected by Google Analytics that can then be used to identify you as an individual. Please see our Cookies Policy for more about how we use Google Analytics. AdvertisingGoogle Adsense is an advertising platform that we use to support the running of this website. As part of this, Adsense (and other third-party advertisers) place cookies on your browser and will display targeted advertising based on your search history. The information collected from these cookies include your IP address, the browser you are using and the device you are using, as well as geolocation (on occasion).This information cannot be used to identify you personally. Nor do we know what adverts have been shown to you. That’s between yourself and your search history. For more information on these cookies and how to disable them, please see our Cookies Policy. You can also use an Ad-Blocker to prevent these adverts from appearing when you visit this site. That’s your call… Social SharingAs far as we can tell, the buttons we use for social sharing are run entirely from this website. They do not collect or store any data, and do not require the use of a third-party service to function. Access to informationYou have the right to access any information that you think we hold about you. Please note that any demand for access is subject to payment of a fee of £10.This covers our costs providing you with the information requested, though we should point out it is highly unlikely that we will hold any data that would give cause for concern.Should you wish to receive details that we hold about you please contact us using the contact details below. Contact usIf you have any queries, comments or requests you have about this policy, drop us a line by emailing us: editor@boroguide.co.ukFor the sake of the legal eagles, the editor of BoroGuide holds the rather lofty title of data controller for this website and the email address above is how to reach us.We do not and will not offer the possibility of contacting us by post or telephone. It’s enough having your email address on file; don’t throw in an address or phone number too. So, we’d appreciate your understanding in this matter.Share The LoveLatest ResultSaturday 05 December 2020
H FL2 Southend United
0-0
CategoriesCategoriesSelect Category10 Of The Best5 Of The BestA Load Of Old ToffeeBoroGuideCapital One CupCharityClose Season BluesCompetitionCult ClassicEnd of Season AwardsFA CupFIFA 18 VerdictFIFA 20 VerdictFootballGet With The ProgrammeGood GameHistoryHouse of Boro’How To…In Collaboration With…InterviewJPTLate Night ThinkingsLeague CupLeague OneLeague TwoLeasing.com TrophyManagersMy Favourite PlayerNon-LeagueOld FriendsPartner PostPlayersPost-Match AnalysisRemember ThemStat AttackStevenageThe Monday RantThere He Is!Transfer TalkUncategorisedUnsung HeroesWatchWhere Are They Now?Who The Hell Was…
StatattackLive football scores . Current table, fixtures & results.
AboutAdvertiseCookiesPressPrivacy © 2012- BoroGuide - All rights reserved.
